## PHEONIX AGENCY

沈阳市

lionking921117@gmail.com

13082428932

If you need a senior full stack developer, I CAN HELP! Here's how: I own a digital agency and you will have both me and my team working with you! We'll help you grow a sustainable business with innovative solutions. I have over 10 years of deep experience with developing large scale web applications using Python/Django PHP, Laravel, Wordpress, JavaScript,React/Angular/Vue and GCP/AWS/AZure. Some of ours core expertise and technologies include Android/los/ lonic, Object C, Node.js & AngularJS, TypeScript, Web Standards / HTML5/ CSS, Web Component, REST API, Json, ngrx, WebPack, Payment Gateway Integration,MySQL/MS SQL other related technologies. My team is just as good. Our agency is based out of Shenyang, China and I am easily accessible during US business hours. If you have a web development project that needs to be completed on time and on spec then please get in touch. We can discuss your needs and how best to get you a solution that works within your budget and expectations. We can get on a call to discuss your project anytime. Our goal is to understand your requirements and give you an honest opinion about what's possible within your budget and needs. Even if we don't end up working together you will walk away with insights that will help you successfully complete your project.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer



## WORK EXPERIENCE ------

## **Mobile Application Developer**

Information Technology Institute(ITI) - Shenyang, Liaoning

September 2017 to Present

I've participated in mobile application development with my team and delivered many apps to the client include social, Fintech, Food delivery &Logistics, Healthcare, Dating, Sport Betting, Mini app.

I was expertises in native/hybrid application development and am familiar with React Native/React/Ionic/Android.

(https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.pickstream&hl=en US

https://apps.apple.com/us/app/scores-odds-by-onside-sports/id637030094)

I built the apps from scratch or plug into the process at any stage the client want me to.

I worked as following stage of working.

Analyze

First of all, I created specifications and guidelines analyzing the custormer's business flows and users' needs to build convenient mobile apps

Make prototypes

We work on the use cases to develop fleshed-out concepts that will stand for a fusion of form, functionality, and effectiveness.

Design

We apply the mobile platforms guidelines to the brand identity and make a beautiful and user-friendly app design. Develop We create an extensible architecture and write a clean and stable code. We integrate with the technologies of our clients. • QA We perform manual functional testing and create UI-autotests. We prepare checklists and test cases. Support We work under the SLA. We monitor the stability of the application work and make the apps ready for new devices and iOS and Android versions. **Full Stack Web Developer** Shenyang Tesai Information Technology Co.,Ltd. July 2013 to March 2017 Our Agency have participated in many Web and mobile development for the clients in the Worldwide Scope and established a lot of digital Products so that optimizing the functionality of the business and get the real benefit in their business. Here's how; -Web Application Development: ✓ Python/Django/Node ✓ PHP/Laravel/CodeIgnitor ✓ Ajax/.Net/SQL/HTML/CSS/Bootstrap ✓ AWS/Azure/GCP & Web Hosting ✓ React/Angular/Vue frontend ✓ Chatbot Service ✓ Wordpress -Moblie Application Development ✓ Android/Ios apps ✓ React Native apps ✓ Ionic hybrid apps

https://imorapidtransfer.com/

Portfolio

✓ Java, Swift, Object C apps

https:// linktracker.pro /		
https://www.website.comunenews.broxlab.com/		
https://clouds.sa/		
http://gardenlandltd.co.uk /		
	<b>⊗</b> 1	
	EDUCATION	
Bachelor's degree in Computer Programming		
Shenyang University of technology - Shenyang,Liaoning September 2009 to June 2013		
	<b>Ö</b>	
	SKILLS	
• APIs		

- Bootstrap
- CSS
- Git
- JavaScript
- MySQL
- Node.js
- REST
- Python
- Django
- PHP
- Django
- React
- Angular
- MongoDB
- Nodejs
- AWS
- Azure
- android
- React Native
- Java
- · Object-C
- Swift
- WordPress
- laravel